Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/haunguyen-46047b229 (LinkedIn) haunguyen.webflow.io (Portfolio) www.behance.net/jay_5695 (Other)

Top Skills

UI/UX Design Adobe Creative Suite Design

Certifications

Build Wireframes and Low-Fidelity Prototypes

Google UX Design Certificate

Design a User Experience for Social Good & Prepare for Jobs

Create High-Fidelity Designs and Prototypes in Figma

Responsive Web Design in Adobe XD

Hau Nguyen

UI/UX Designer @ Freelance | Multi Media Design Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Full of enthusiatic and passionate UI/UX and Graphic designer, with years of experience in create design that are not only visually beautiful, but can provide real value to clients. Have a high passion for delivering on-trend designs to effectively increate the brand's identity and value. Knowledgeable of UI/UX and Graphic design, and proficient in a combination both of them. Bring the skills, experience and ability to handle all aspects of a design from conception to completion.

Experience

Freelance
UI/UX Designer (Freelance)
January 2020 - Present (5 years 3 months)

Freelance

Graphic Designer
January 2019 - Present (6 years 3 months)

Online digital marketing design, Web-UI/UX design, 2D graphic design, Social media post design, Printable-Packaging design

BREAK FIELD VIETNAM

Creative Team Lead November 2019 - June 2023 (3 years 8 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Social media post design, Animation design, Web design, Design solutions provider, Responsibility for Design team

Viet Beauties Graphic Designer October 2018 - October 2019 (1 year 1 month) Ho Chi Minh city, Viet Nam

Social media post design, Video filming, Animation design, Online marketing design, Photographer, Packging design

Page 1 of 2

Education

FPT Arena - Multi Media - Ho Chi Minh city - Viet Nam Advanced, Multi Media Design · (June 2016 - December 2018)